lifeleadership.com 2017-12-28

# Privacy Policy | LIFE Leadership

Life (referred to herein as “Life” or __ the "Company") created this Privacy Policy to give you confidence as you visit and use our Websites or Mobile Applications, and to demonstrate its commitment to fair information practices and to the protection of privacy. 

This Privacy Policy is only applicable to this Website and Mobile Application, and not to any Third-Party Websites or Mobile Applications, which may have data collection, storage and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy. For additional information, see the section concerning Third-Party Websites or Mobile Applications, below. 

BY USING THE WEBSITE OR MOBILE APPLICATION, YOU REPRESENT AND WARRANT THAT YOU HAVE READ AND UNDERSTOOD, AND AGREE TO THE TERMS OF, THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT UNDERSTAND OR DO NOT AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU MUST IMMEDIATELY LEAVE THE WEBSITE OR MOBILE APPLICATION. 

Each time you use the Website or Mobile Application, the then-current version of this Privacy Policy will apply. Accordingly, each time you use the Website or Mobile Application you should check the date of this Privacy Policy (which appears at the end) and review any changes since the last time you visited the Website or Mobile Application. For additional information, see the section concerning Updates and Changes to Privacy Policy, below. 

**1\. CHILDREN'S PRIVACY**

The Website or Mobile Application is not directed to children under the age of 13. Life does not solicit or knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If Life obtains actual knowledge that it has collected personally identifiable information from a child under the age of 13, Life will delete such information from its database. Because Life does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, Life does not use or disclose such information to third parties. Life has designed this Privacy Policy to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Act (COPPA). 

**2\. INFORMATION COLLECTION PRACTICES**

a. **Traffic Data.** Like most website or mobile application operators, Life automatically gathers information of the sort that browsers automatically make available, including: (i) IP addresses; (ii) domain servers; (iii) types of devices accessing the Website or Mobile Application; and (iv) types of Web browsers accessing the Website (collectively "Traffic Data"). Traffic Data is anonymous information that does not personally identify you. 

b. **Cookies.** A "Cookie" is a string of information that a website stores on a user's computer, and that the user's browser provides to the website each time the user submits a query to the website. The purpose of a Cookie is to identify the user as a unique user of the Website but not to gather personal information about the user. Life uses Cookies to customize your experience on the Website to your interests, to ensure that you do not see the same informational messages repeatedly, and to store your username so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit the Website. Overall, cookies are safe, as they only identify your computer to customize your Web experience. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually adjust your settings to notify you of cookie placement requests, refuse certain cookies, or decline cookies completely. If you turn off cookies, you assume all responsibility for any resulting loss of functionality. For additional information on Life's uses of Cookies, see the section concerning Information Use and Disclosure Practices/Traffic Data and Information Gathered Using Cookies, below. 

c. **Personal Information.** For you to use certain Services, you may be asked to provide Life certain information that identifies you ("Personal Information"). Personal Information includes, without limitation: (1) "Contact Data" (such as your name, mailing address and e-mail address); (2) "Demographic Data" (such as your age, gender, profession, education level, relationship status, religious affiliation, country, state, city and likes and dislikes,); and (3) "Financial Data" (such as your credit/debit card number and expiration date). In each case, you will be asked to provide Personal information; the Website or Mobile Application will not gather it surreptitiously. Life may supplement the Personal Information you provide with additional Personal Information gathered from public sources or from third-parties (e.g., consumer reporting agencies) who may lawfully provide such information to Life. You are under no obligation to provide Personal Information, with the caveat that your refusal to do so may prevent you from using certain features and services available on the Website or Mobile Application. 

d. **Information you Make Public on the Website or Mobile Application.** The Website or Mobile Application may contain features (e.g. public profiles, forums, and message boards) that permit you to upload, post, transmit, display, perform or distribute content, information or other material, including your Personal Information. Any information that you choose to disclose by means of such features becomes public information over which Life is unable to exercise control. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your Personal Information by means of such features, and you agree to assume all responsibility for doing so. 

**3\. INFORMATION USE AND DISCLOSURE PRACTICES**

a. **Traffic Data and Information Gathered Using Cookies.** Life analyzes Traffic Data and information gathered using Cookies to help Life better understand who is using the Website and how they are using it. By identifying patterns and trends in usage, Life is able to better design the Website to improve your experience, and to serve you more relevant and interesting content. From time to time, Life may release Traffic Data and information gathered using Cookies in the aggregate, such as by publishing a report on trends in the usage of the Website. Life does not attempt to link information gathered using Cookies to Personal Information. 

b. **Personal Information**

i. **Generally.** Life uses your Contact Data to send you information about Life, Life's products and services, Life's marketing and sales and your orders of Life's products and services. Life uses your Financial Data to bill you. Life uses your Demographic Data to customize and tailor your experience on the Websites and Mobile Applications. As with Traffic Data and information gathered using Cookies, from time to time Life may release Demographic Data in the aggregate, such as by publishing a report on trends in the usage of this Website or Mobile Applications. 

ii. **Disclosure Practices.** Except under the following circumstances and otherwise as set forth in this Privacy Policy, Life will keep your Personal Information private and will not sell it to or share it with third parties. 

· Disclosure in Connection with Services. Life discloses Personal Information to those who help it provide Services, including those who perform technical, administrative and data processing tasks such as hosting, billing, fulfillment, and data storage and security. 

· By Law or to Protect Rights. Life discloses Personal Information when required to do so by law, or in response to a subpoena or court order, or when Life believes in its sole discretion that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Life, third parties or the public at large. 

· Business Transfers; Bankruptcy. Life reserves the right to transfer all Personal Information in its possession to a successor organization in the event of a merger, acquisition, or bankruptcy or other sale of all or a portion of Life's assets. Other than to the extent ordered by a bankruptcy or other court, the use and disclosure of all transferred Personal Information will be subject to this Privacy Policy, or to a new privacy policy if you are given notice of that new privacy policy and an opportunity to affirmatively opt-out of it. Personal Information submitted or collected after a transfer, however, may be subject to a new privacy policy adopted by Life's successor organization. 

· Unpaid Accounts. If you fail to pay any balance owed in consideration of Services, Life may, as permitted by law, report your Personal Information, including without limitation your unpaid balance, to consumer credit reporting services, collection agencies and others. 

**4\. CONSENT TO RECEIVE COMMUNICATIONS FROM LIFE**

By registering with the Website, you thereby consent to receive periodic email and other communications from Life regarding policies, new product offers, promotions and other matters. If you desire not to receive e-mails, you may opt-out by following the unsubscribe instructions within each e-mail communication or submit your request to lifesupport@lifeleadership.com. 

**5\. SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Life has implemented and maintains reasonable security procedures and practices to protect against the unauthorized access, use, modification, destruction or disclosure of your Personal Information. 

**6\. LOST OR STOLEN INFORMATION**

You must promptly notify us if your credit, banking, other financial information, user name or password is lost, stolen or used without permission. In such an event, we will remove that credit card number, bank account information, other financial institution information, user name or password from your account. 

**7\. USER ABILITY TO ACCESS, UPDATE, AND CORRECT PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Life wants your Personal Information to be complete and accurate. By using the Website or Mobile Application, you represent and warrant that all information you provide on any registration form or otherwise in connection with your use of the Website or Mobile Application and Services will be complete and accurate, and that you will update that information as necessary to maintain its completeness and accuracy. To confirm the completeness and accuracy of, or make changes to, your Personal Information, visit your Profile. Through your Profile you may review and update your Personal Information. 

**8\. THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES AND MOBILE APPLICATIONS**

Life neither owns nor controls Third-Party Websites or Mobile Applications. Accordingly, Third-Party Websites or Mobile Applications are under no obligation to comply with this Privacy Policy except with respect to Personal Information provided directly to them by Life. Before visiting or providing Personal Information to a Third-Party Website or Mobile Application, you should inform yourself of the privacy policies and practices (if any) of that Third-Party Website or Mobile Application, and should take those steps necessary to, in your discretion, protect your privacy. 

**9\. PROMOTIONAL ACTIVITIES**

From time to time, Life may conduct contests, giveaways and other promotions (collectively, "Promotional Activities"). Any information submitted in connection with Promotional Activities will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy. From time to time, Life may also ask you to participate in surveys designed to help Life improve the Websites or Mobile Applications, its products or services. Any Personal Information provided to Life in connection with any survey will be used only in relation to that survey, and might be disclosed to third parties not bound by this Privacy Policy only in aggregated form. 

**10\. UPDATES AND CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Life reserves the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, update, change or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such update, change or modification on this page. Any such addition, update, change or modification will be posted on the Website or Mobile Application 30 days prior to the effective date of the amendment(s). Each time you use the Website or Mobile Application, the then-current version of this Privacy Policy will apply. Accordingly, each time you use the Website or Mobile Application, you should check the date of this Privacy Policy (which appears at the end) and review any changes since the last time you used the Website or Mobile Application. Unless Life obtains your express consent, any revised Privacy Policy will apply only to information collected after the effective date of such revised Privacy Policy, and not to information collected under any earlier Privacy Policy.
